Guide to the Julia Driver Collection of Women in Photography
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Card Photographs and Other Photographic Materials, 1845-1940; Series II; 5.83
  - Photographic Materials
    - Panneberg, Maria, Mrs. (born 1839), 1894-1900; (5 cabinet photographs) (Box 11, Folder 417)
      Panneberg was a partner with her son-in-law, Hermann Koppelmann (born 1862)
      Active in Chicago, Illinois, 1878-1895
      Also known as H. Koppelmann & Mrs. Panneberg
      Includes a portrait of Robert Vogt (born 1891) in 1894
    - Parks, F., Mrs., circa 1895-1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 418)
      Active in Kendal, England, circa 1895-1900
    - Parsons & Bates, Misses, circa 1889-1895; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 11, Folder 419)
      Active in Iowa Falls, Iowa, circa 1889-1895
      Partnership between Stella Mary Parsons (1866-1949, later Mrs. Gerald Whinery) and Hatta Mildred Bates (1867-1905, later Mrs. John Francis Welden)
    - Parsons, Mary E., Mrs. (born circa 1839), 1872-1883; (17 cartes-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 420)
      Active in Ypsilanti, Michigan, 1872-1883
      Also known as Mrs. J. H. Parsons or Mrs. John H. Parsons
      Includes a portrait of George W. Loughridge (born circa 1844), owner of Ypsilanti Marble and Granite Works, circa 1875
    - Payne, Mary Smith, Mrs. (1842-circa 1912), circa 1875; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 421)
      Active in Aylesbury, Thame, and Tring, England, 1877-1900
      Also known as Mrs. Samuel Glendening Payne
      Includes discrete portraits of a man with a large dog and a family portrait that includes children playing with wooden blocks
    - Pearson, Lula I., Miss (born 1865), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 422)
      Active in Cassopolis and Dowagiac, Michigan, circa 1895-1917
      Portrait of Arthur Scofield (born 1876), Irlena Scofield, and Arthur Scofield
    - Pence, L., Mrs., 1894 July; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 423)
      Active in Colton, California, circa 1894
      Portrait of Steven Robert Culbertson (1848-1915) and Mary Estelle Downer Culbertson (born circa 1858)
    - Perlmutter-Heilperin, Adèle, Mrs., 1871; (1 carte-de-visite and 1 card photograph) (Box 11, Folder 424)
      Active in Vienna, Austria, 1862-1890
      Also known as Adèle Perlmutter, Adèle Atelier, or Studio Adele
    - Persson, Gunni, 1914; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 425)
      Active in Höör, Sweden, circa 1914
    - Peterson, Sophia, Mrs. (circa 1865), circa 1905; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 426)
      Active in Ruthton, Minnesota, circa 1900-1910
    - Petterson, Tora, circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 427)
      Active in Östersund, Sweden, circa 1890
    - Pickett, Annie L., Miss (born 1863), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 428)
      Active in Americus, Georgia, circa 1900
      Also known as Miss A. L. Pickett
    - Podore, Clara Sabo, Mrs. (1863-1947), circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 429)
      Active in Menominee, Michigan, 1890-1891
      Also known as Mrs. Alexandre Podore
    - Pomeroy, L. E., Miss, 1865-1866; (9 cartes-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 430)
      Active in Independence, Iowa, 1865-1866
    - Porter, Lizzie E., (born 1873), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 11, Folder 431)
      Active in Geneseo, Illinois, circa 1900
    - Porter, Margaret, Mrs. (born circa 1841), circa 1875; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 11, Folder 432)
      Active in Perth, Scotland, circa 1875
      Also known as Mrs. J. Porter or Mrs. James Porter
    - Porter, Minnie E., Mrs. (born 1869), 1911 December; (1 photographic print) (Box 11, Folder 433)
      Active in Cozad, Nebraska, circa 1910
      Also known as Mrs. M. E. Porter
      Portrait of Helen Hunt Brown (born 1910) with her mother, Dolly Brown (born circa 1871)
    - Prentice, Ellen A., Miss (born circa 1863), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 12, Folder 434)
      Active in Clay Center, Nebraska, circa 1890-1910
    - Proctor, Helen M., Mrs. (born circa 1829), 1860-1869; (6 cartes-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 435)
      Active in Smyrna, New York, 1860-1869
      Also known as Mrs. H. M. Proctor or Mrs. Rufus Proctor
    - Prod'hom, Camille, Madame, circa 1860-1870; (2 cartes-de-visite and 2 cabinet photographs) (Box 12, Folder 436)
      Active in Bône (Annaba), Algeria, circa 1860-1870
      Also known as Madame Jean Prod'hom
      Includes views of a plateau and a Bedouin market at Souk Ahras, Algeria
    - Purvis, Lizzie Miller, Mrs., circa 1905; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 12, Folder 437)
      Active in Roscommon and Rose City, Michigan, circa 1905
      Also known as Mrs. E. P. Purvis
      Includes portraits of Floyd Sargeant
    - Radcliffe, Margaret N., Mrs. (born circa 1864), circa 1905; (3 cabinet photographs) (Box 12, Folder 438)
      Active in Ashton-under-Lyne and Hyde, England, 1901-1913
      Also known as Mrs. Sam. Radcliffe or Mrs. Samuel Radcliffe
    - Raimheld, Harriett Bullis, Mrs. (1837-1913), 1876-1880; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 439)
      Active in Morrison, Iowa; Clinton, Iowa; Warren, Minnesota; and Fort Atkinson, Wisconsin, 1876-1880
      Also known as Mrs. H. E. Raimheld or Mrs. Henry E. Raimheld
      Includes a portrait of journalist-poet George Washington Bungay (1818-1892)
    - Rainer, Camilla von, circa 1884; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 440)
      Active in Vienna, Austria, circa 1884
    - Ranch, Mathilda, circa 1895; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 441)
      Active in Slöinge and Varberg, Sweden, 1888-1915
    - Randall, Charlotte, Mrs. (born circa 1846), circa 1866-1870; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 442)
      Active in Clyde, Ohio, circa 1866-1870
      Also known as Mrs. J. H. Randall
    - Rathbun, Matilda Tyler, Mrs. (1834-1909), 1868-1875; (7 cartes-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 443)
      Active in Foster, Lincoln, Pawtucket, and Rockland, Rhode Island, 1868-1875
      Also known as Mrs. G. W. Rathbun or Mrs. George W. Rathbun
    - Rattan, Amanda E., Mrs. (born circa 1839), circa 1870; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 444)
      Active in Kirksville, Missouri, circa 1870
      Also known as Mrs. A. E. Rattan or Mrs. Thomas Rattan
    - Rea, Josephine H., Miss (1883-1951), circa 1885-1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 12, Folder 445)
      Active in Baker City, Oregon, circa 1885-1895
      Also known as Miss Josie H. Rea or Mrs. Lawrence Creath Ammons
    - Reed, Candace McCormick, Mrs. (1818-1900), circa 1885; (23 cartes-de-visite and 5 cabinet photographs) (Box 12, Folder 446)
      Active in Quincy, Illinois, as well as Canton, La Grange, and Palmyra, Missouri, 1848-1888
    - Rhodes, Augusta A., Mrs., circa 1865-1866; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 447)
      Active in Rockford, Illinois, circa 1865-1866
      Also known as Mrs. A. A. Rhodes
    - Rich, Elizabeth, Mrs., 1883-1887; (2 cartes-de-visite and 1 cabinet photograph) (Box 12, Folder 448)
      Active in Zanesville, Ohio, 1883-1887
      Also known as Mrs. S. A. Rich or Mrs. Samuel A. Rich
      Includes a portrait of Cordelia B. Mote Erven (born 1852), probably created by her husband, Arabsalon A. J. Erven (born 1853), an operator at the studio. Also includes portraits of brothers Thadius Tanner (born circa 1859) and Josiah Tanner (born circa 1857)
    - Roach, Iva, Miss (born circa 1868), circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 12, Folder 449)
      Active in Cicero, Indiana, circa 1890
    - Robinson, Lorena Gorham, Mrs. (1843-1931), circa 1890; (10 cabinet photographs and 2 photographic prints) (Box 12, Folder 450)
      Active in New York City, circa 1890
      Also known as Mrs. W. A. Robinson or Mrs. William A. Robinson
    - Robinson, Margaret, Mrs. (circa 1824-1899), circa 1870-1875; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 451)
      Active in Dukinfield and Ashton-under-Lyne, England, circa 1870-1875
      Also known as Mrs. William Robinson
      Includes a portrait of John Tyson Hibbert
    - Robison, Catherine Malinda White, Mrs. (born 1840), circa 1875; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 452)
      Active in Hillsboro, Illinois, circa 1875
      Also known as Mrs. N. A. Robinson, Mrs. Ninian Alexander Robison, or Mrs. Franklin Larrabee
    - Rogerson, Hannah, Miss (born circa 1825), circa 1865; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 453)
      Active in Newport, Wales, circa 1865
      Portrait of Reverend E. C. Jenkins, D.D.
    - Rosdahl, Elin, circa 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 454)
      Active in Östersund, Sweden, circa 1900-1910
    - Rosendahl, Hedvig, circa 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 455)
      Active in Stockholm, Sweden, 1891-1909
    - Ross, Susan H., Miss (born circa 1829), circa 1866-1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 456)
      Active in Middlebury, Vermont, circa 1864-1870
      Also known as Miss S. H. Ross
    - Rossiter, L. M. & T. E., Misses, circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph and 1 card photograph) (Box 12, Folder 457)
      Partnership between sisters Elizabeth "Lizzie" Rossiter (born 1856) and Matilda "Tillie" Rossiter (born 1858)
      Active in St. Ansgar, Iowa, circa 1888-1928
    - Royce, Roana, Mrs. (born circa 1843), circa 1865-1875; (22 cartes-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 458)
      Active in Willimantic and Stafford Springs, Connecticut, circa 1865-1875
      Also known as Mrs. H. Royce or Mrs. Henry F. Royce
      Includes a portrait of Emaline Fenton (born circa 1845) from Argyle, New York
    - Rudolph, Julia Ann, Mrs. (circa 1820-1900), circa 1866; (6 cartes-de-visite and 1 cabinet photograph) (Box 12, Folder 459)
      Active in Nevada City and Sacramento, California, as well as Utica, New York, circa 1852-1890
      Also a partner in Quirk & Rudolph in Nevada City, California, probably with James Quirk
      Also known as Miss Julia Ann Swift, Mrs. Rudolph Hopkins Raymond, or Mrs. James Ferdinand Rudolph
      Includes a portrait that probably depicts Eustace Joseph Price (born circa 1865) in 1866
    - Russell, B. H., Mrs., circa 1860-1869; (5 cartes-de-visite) (Box 12, Folder 460)
      Active in Moodus, Connecticut, circa 1860-1869
    - Russell, Catharine Saxe, Mrs. (born 1853), circa 1880-1900; (4 cabinet photographs) (Box 12, Folder 461)
      Active in Cresco, Iowa, as well as Canton, Mable, and Harmony, Minnesota, circa 1880-1900
      Also known as Mrs. Katie Russell, Mrs. Frank E. Russell, or Mrs. F. E. Russell & Son
    - Ryding, Nellie E., Miss (born 1875), circa 1895; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 12, Folder 462)
      Active in Candor, Newfield, Spencer, and Tully, New York, 1889-1905
      Also known as Miss N. E. Ryding
    - Sangunitta, S., Mrs., circa 1905; (1 tintype) (Box 13, Folder 463)
      Active in Coney Island, New York, circa 1905
    - Schellhous, Martha Catherine Faxon, Mrs. (born 1831), circa 1864; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 464)
      Active in Ada, Coldwater, and Grand Rapids, Michigan, circa 1864-1890
      Also known as Mrs. L. W. Schellhous or Mrs. Loren W. Schellhous
    - Schilling, Louise, circa 1880; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 465)
      Active in Vienna, Austria, circa 1880
    - Schmid, L., Miss, circa 1900; (1 card photograph) (Box 13, Folder 466)
      Active in Greenwood, Indiana, circa 1900
    - Schooley, Lydia A. Gochnaur, Mrs. (1839-1923), 1879-1897; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 467)
      Active in Indianola, Iowa, 1879-1897
      Also known as Mrs. William Henry Schooley
    - Schou, Augusta, circa 1910; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 468)
      Active in Bornholm, Denmark, circa 1910
    - Scott, A. L., Mrs., circa 1890-circa 1900; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 13, Folder 469)
      Active in Oxford, New York, circa 1890-1900
      Includes a portrait of a woman with a spinning wheel
    - Scott, Hannah E., Miss (born 1871), circa 1905; (1 photographic print) (Box 13, Folder 470)
      Active in Independence, Kansas, circa 1900-1930
    - Sears, Ariadne Barnes, Mrs. (born circa 1824), circa 1860-1869; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 471)
      Active in Camden, New York, circa 1860-1869
      Also known as Mrs. D. Sears or Mrs. David Sears
    - Sittler, Elizabeth Middlesworth, Mrs. (born 1850), circa 1887; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 472)
      Active in Springfield, Missouri, circa 1887
      Also known as Mrs. G. W. Sittler or Mrs. George W. Sittler
    - Sjöman, Rosalie, 1873; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 473)
      Active in Stockholm, Sweden, circa 1870-1901
      Hand colored portraits of Swedish women in ethnic costumes
    - Slater, A., Mrs., circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 474)
      Active in Waterford, Ireland, circa 1870
    - Smith, Catherine A. N., Mrs. (born 1820), circa 1870-1888; (2 cartes-de-visite, 1 cabinet photograph, and 1 tintype) (Box 13, Folder 475)
      Active in New York City, circa 1870-1888
      Also known as Mrs. C. A. N. Smith
    - Smith, Costillia D., Miss (born 1830-1905), circa 1880-1889; (16 cartes-de-visite and 2 cabinet photographs) (Box 13, Folder 476)
      Active in Lowell, Massachusetts, circa 1880-1889
      Also known as Mrs. C. Smith
    - Smith, Elizabeth Belle Johnson, Mrs. (born 1857), circa 1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 477)
      Active in Ida Grove, Iowa, circa 1885
      Also known as Mrs. B. Smith, Mrs. Dwight Smith, or Mrs. N. Hansen
    - Smith, Mary E., Mrs. (born 1857), circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 478)
      Active in Chanute, Kansas, circa 1900
      Also known as Maters Art Studio
    - Smith, Rebecca Ann Mason, Mrs. (circa 1821-1882), circa 1864-1869; (13 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 479)
      Active in Carlisle, Pennsylvania, 1856-1882
      Also known as Mrs. Reynolds, Mrs. R. A. Smith, or Mrs. William Gayley Smith
      Includes a portrait of Brevet Brigadier-General Joseph J.B. Wright (died 1878), a military surgeon for the United States Army during the American Civil War
    - Smorthwaite, Emma, Mrs. (1840-1922), circa 1885; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 480)
      Active in London, England, 1876-1894
      Also known as Mrs. William Smorthwaite or Mrs. Charles Alfred Bungey
    - Speechley, Susan T., Miss (born circa 1844), circa 1870-1880; (6 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 481)
      Active in Manchester and Ann Arbor, Michigan, circa 1870-1880
      Also known as Miss S. T. Speechly
    - Spence & McClave, Misses, circa 1870-1880; (6 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 482)
      Partnership between Miss Sallie McClave (born circa 1842) and Miss Spence
      Active in Buckley, Illinois, circa 1870-1880
    - Sprauer, Apollonia Schmitt, Mrs. (1851-1911), circa 1890; (3 cabinet photographs) (Box 13, Folder 483)
      Active in Huntingburg, Indiana, 1880-1900
      Also known as Mrs. Jos. Sprauer or Mrs. Joseph Alowicioius Sprauer
    - Sprengel, Elma, circa 1890; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 484)
      Active in Cottbus, Brandenburg, circa 1890
    - Stebbins, Sarah Ann Landis, Mrs. (born circa 1833), circa 1870; (6 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 485)
      Also known as Mrs. S. L. Stebbins or Mrs. Benton Pixley Stebbins
    - Steele, Mrs., circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 486)
      Active in the United States of America, circa 1870
      Also known as Red Jacket Art Gallery
    - Stephanie, circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 487)
      Active in Liesing, Austria, circa 1895
      Portrait of a small child with a dog
    - Sterling, Hannah N. Auld, Mrs. (born circa 1827), circa 1870-1880; (11 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 488)
      Active in Eaton and Niles, Michigan, circa 1870-1880
      Also known as Mrs. Ossian Auld, Mrs. H. N. Sterling, or Mrs. H. N. Stirling
      Includes a portrait of Warren Toney (born 1860) of Berrien, Michigan, circa 1880
    - Stevenson, E. F., Mrs., circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 489)
      Active in Sterling, Illinois, circa 1890-1899
    - Stickney, Martha J., Mrs. (born circa 1848), circa 1880; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 490)
      Active in Edmeston and Morris, New York, circa 1880
      Also known as Mrs. L. Stickney or Mrs. Laroy Stickney
    - Stokes, Emily, Mrs. (born 1829), circa 1881-1904; (7 cabinet photographs and 1 card photograph) (Box 13, Folder 491)
      Active in Boston, Massachusetts, circa 1881-1904
      Includes portraits of Ethel Gray Robert Howard and D. F. Spinney
    - Stone, Susannah, Mrs. (born 1830), circa 1865-1870; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 492)
      Active in Woodhull, New York, circa 1865-1870
      Also known as Mrs. T. P. Stone or Mrs. Thomas P. Stone
    - Strom, Marie, circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 493)
      Active in Sheldahl, Iowa, circa 1895
    - Stuart, Helen F., Mrs., circa 1862-1866; (3 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 494)
      Active in Boston, Massachusetts, circa 1862-1866
      Also known as Mrs. H. F. Stuart or Mrs. A. M. Stuart
      Includes a copy photograph of a daguerreotype portrait of Jonathan Fuller
    - Sutcliffe, Elizabeth Eleanor Jackson, Mrs. (born 1849), circa 1898; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 495)
      Active in Burton, England, circa 1891-1901
      Also known as Mrs. John Francis Sutcliffe
    - Svensund, Marie, circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 496)
      Active in Sæby, Denmark, circa 1895
    - Swan, E. F., Mrs., circa 1885; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 497)
      Active in Glens Falls, New York, circa 1885
    - Swensson, Alma, 1906-1918; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 498)
      Active in Karlskrona, Sweden, circa 1905-1916
      Portrait of a sailor in uniform and posing with an anchor set piece
    - Swift, S. J., Mrs., circa 1885; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 499)
      Active in Newark, New Jersey, circa 1885
    - Taylor, Caroline Pharmelia Bunker, Mrs. (born 1854), circa 1885; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 500)
      Active in Saint Paul, Minnesota, 1886-1888
      Also known as Mrs. S. M. Taylor or Mrs. Schuyler M. Taylor
    - Ten Eyck, M. C., Mrs., circa 1866; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 501)
      Active in Milwaukee, Wisconsin, circa 1865-1870
    - Tesch, Maria, (circa 1850-1936), circa 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 502)
      Active in Linköping, Sweden, 1873-1936
    - Thompson, Rosalie, Mrs. (1831-1923), 1872-1878; (5 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 503)
      Active in Ottawa, Illinois, 1872-1878
      Also known as Mrs. George C. Thompson, Mrs. Rosella Thompson, Mrs. Rosalin Thompson, or Mrs. Rosalia Thompson
    - Thornley, Cordelia A., Miss (born circa 1877), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 13, Folder 504)
      Active in White City, Kansas, circa 1895
      Portrait of a man playing a guitar
    - Tillander, Jenny, circa 1900; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 505)
      Active in Alvesta and Grännaforsa, Sweden, circa 1900-1910
    - Timms, Anne Pearce, Mrs. (circa 1827-1874), 1866-1867; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 13, Folder 506)
      Active in London, England, 1857-1867
      Also known as Mrs. Charles Alfred Timms
    - Tipton, Annie, Mrs., circa 1900; (1 tintype) (Box 13, Folder 507)
      Active in Greenfield, Illinois, circa 1900
      Portrait of George L. Hand (born circa 1874) of Greene County, Illinois
    - Towne & Whitney, circa 1890; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 14, Folder 508)
      Partnership between Anna F. Wing Towne (1854-1952, Mrs. Willis Towne) and Alma Whitney (born 1862)
      Active in Ashburnham, Athol, Gardner, Northfield, and West Gardner, Massachusetts, 1887-1898
      Includes a portrait of a boy posed reclining and holding a cello
    - Townsend, Louisa A., Mrs. (born 1857), circa 1877-1880; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 14, Folder 509)
      Active in Conneautville and Sharon, Pennsylvania, circa 1877-1880
      Also known as Mrs. Abram P. Townsend
    - Train, Phebe Goodell, Mrs. (born circa 1850), circa 1870; (4 cartes-de-visite) (Box 14, Folder 510)
      Active in Helena, Montana, circa 1870
      Also known as Mrs. E. H. Train or Mrs. Edgar H. Train
    - Treganowan, Matilda, Miss (born circa 1842), circa 1871; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 14, Folder 511)
      Active in Tottenham, England, circa 1871
    - Trindall, Laura, Miss (born circa 1864), circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 14, Folder 512)
      Active in Pembroke Dock, Wales, circa 1891-1901
    - Turnbull, Misses, circa 1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 14, Folder 513)
      Partnership between sisters Nellie A. Turnbull (born 1877) and Nettie M. Turnbull (born 1874)
      Active in Carlinville, Illinois, circa 1900
    - Turner, Edna E., Miss (born 1875), circa 1898; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 14, Folder 514)
      Active in Pittsford, Michigan, circa 1898-1910
      Also known as Mrs. John H. Church
    - Turner, Sarah, Mrs. (born circa 1843), circa 1885; (1 tintype) (Box 14, Folder 515)
      Active in Creighton, Nebraska, circa 1885
      Also known as Mrs. A. V. Turner or Mrs. Andrew V. Turner
    - Turney, Jane, Mrs. (born circa 1836), circa 1870-1875; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 14, Folder 516)
      Active in Islington, England, circa 1861-1879
      Also known as Mrs. William Turney
    - Tyler, May E. Willis, Mrs. (1851-1892), 1886-1892; (1 carte-de-visite and 2 cabinet photographs) (Box 14, Folder 517)
      Active in Ashland, Oregon, 1886-1892
      Also known as Mrs. Eugene Tyler
    - Valerius, Aurora Valeria Albertina, (1824-1895), circa 1870; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 14, Folder 518)
      Active in Sweden, circa 1860-1872
      Also known as Berta Valerius or Bertha Valerius
    - Vallet, Mary, Mrs. (born circa 1838), 1860-1866; (2 cartes-de-visite) (Box 14, Folder 519)
      Active in Kingston, New York, 1860-1866
      Also known as Mary [no surname] or Mrs. George Vallet
    - Van Dusen, Elizabeth Jane Jones, Mrs. (1845-1938), circa 1895-1900; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 14, Folder 520)
      Active in Hope, North Dakota, circa 1895-1900
      Also known as Mrs. D. N. Van Dusen or Mrs. Daniel Nirum Van Dusen
    - Van Housen, Mary E. Lewis, Mrs. (born circa 1840), circa 1860-1880; (9 cartes-de-visite) (Box 14, Folder 521)
      Active in Bath, Hammondsport, and Prattsburgh, New York, circa 1860-1880
      Also known as Mrs. M. E. Van Housen or Mrs. Charles H. Van Housen
    - Vance, Harriet S., Miss (1867-1950), circa 1900; (2 cabinet photographs) (Box 14, Folder 522)
      Active in Pontiac, Illinois, circa 1900
    - Viall, Matilda, Mrs. (1854-1932), circa 1895; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 14, Folder 523)
      Active in Bloomingdale, Douglas, Gobleville, and Penn, Michigan, circa 1890-1900
      Also known as Mrs. F. M. Viall or Mrs. Frank M. Viall
    - Vogelsang, E., Frau, circa 1890; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 14, Folder 524)
      Active in Berlin, Germany, 1868-1897
      Portrait of a woman dressed in an Egyptian-style costume
    - Vreeland, Rosana E. Burgess, Mrs. (born 1853), circa 1885; (2 cartes-de-visite and 4 cabinet photographs) (Box 14, Folder 525)
      Active in McPherson, Kansas, 1885-1900
      Also known as Mrs. Rosa Vreeland, Mrs. Cornelius Vreeland, and Mrs. Vreeland-Whitlock
    - Wade, Frances A., Miss (born circa 1857), 1890-1898; (1 cabinet photograph) (Box 14, Folder 526)
      Active in Rockland, Maine, 1890-1898
    - Wadsworth, Sarah J. Witherill, Mrs. (born 1841), circa 1860-1869; (5 cartes-de-visite) (Box 14, Folder 527)
      Active in Franklin, New Hampshire, circa 1860-1869
      Also known as Mrs. Wm. B. Wadsworth or Mrs. William Booth Wadsworth
    - Waldack, Mary, Mrs. (born circa 1849), circa 1880; (1 carte-de-visite and 2 cabinet photographs) (Box 14, Folder 528)
      Active in Cincinnati, Ohio, circa 1885-1890
      Also known as Mrs. Charles Waldack
    - Wallgren, Therése, circa 1895; (1 carte-de-visite) (Box 14, Folder 529)